Class of 1972 Records, 1968-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1972 Records
1968-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1972.
RG 80 UUID:f128362f-514e-4d14-902d-b790d5a04fef
4 boxes (1.5 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1972.
The Class of 1972 was the ninety-fourth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1972 records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1972, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1972 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- General 1967-1972 (Box 2253, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1972 (Box 2253, Folder 2)
- Commencement Photographs 1972 (Box 2253, Folder 3)
- Commencement Speaker 1972 (Box 2253, Folder 4)
- Freshman Handbook 1968-1969 (Box 2253, Folder 5)
- Groups 1972 (Box 2253, Folder 6)
- History 1968-1972 (Box 2253, Folder 7)
- Ivy Day 1972 (Box 2253, Folder 8)
- Class Letters 1973, 2003-2004 (Box 2253, Folder 9)
- Last Chapel 1972 (Box 2253, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1977, 1982 (Box 2253, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1992, 1997, 2002 (Box 2253, Folder 12)
- Will 1972 (Box 2253, Folder 13)